Now if we run Hardhead test, let's just test everything together right now.
现在如果我们运行 `hh test` 直接测试所有的内容
And everything is passing. Oh, this is wonderful.
哦~ 全都通过了，真是太爽了
Awesome. Let's keep it going.
好极了，让我们继续前进
And if we run Hardhead coverage, we'll see our coverage is bumping up,
如果我们运行 `hh coverage` 就会看到覆盖率正在提高
we are already drastically better than where we were before.
目前的覆盖率已经远远超过了之前的水平
Let's keep going well, let's go ahead and test our check upkeep now.
现在让我们继续前进，测试一下我们的 "checkUpkeep"
So we'll do describe, check upkeep. And this will be an async function,
我们执行 `describe("checkUpkeep")` 这里是一个 `async function`
where we'll say it returns false. If people have been sent an E, E,
这里面写 `it("returns false if people haven't sent any ETH")
it's been a sync function.
这里是一个 "async function"
So we'll have everything in here be true except for the fact that nobody's entered yet.
这里的所有内容都是 true 不过事实上并没有人参与
So we'll do a weight network dot provider dot send EVM increase time, comma interval.to number plus one
所以我们执行 `await network.provider.send("evn_increaseTime", [interval.toNumber() +1])
will do a weight network dot provider. That send UVM mine. No parameters.
再执行 `await network.provider.send("evm_mine")` 没有参数